Carl Oglesby Papers, 1942-2005
Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 6: Personal, 1942-2003
  - Correspondence: publishing, 1978-1992 (Box 55)
  - Correspondence: Rutgers University Press, 1993-2001 (Box 55)
  - Correspondence: Woods, Phil, 2002 (Box 55)
  - Correspondence: Wrestling, Alma, 1966-1988 (Box 55)
  - Excerpts: The Peacemaker, undated (Box 55)
  - Lease information, 2002-2003 (Box 55)
  - Name tags and tickets, 1990-1997 (Box 55)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1954-2001 (Box 55)
  - Notes, undated (Box 56)
  - Notes, undated (Box 56)
  - "Killers" calendar materials, circa 1995; Oglesby, Caleb (Box 56)
  - Oglesby family history, 1962-1994 (Box 56)
  - Oglesby family legal papers, 1942-1997 (Box 56)
  - Poetry: Oglesby, Aron, 1978 (Box 56)
  - Poetry: Oglesby, Carl, circa 1990 (Box 56)
  - Photographs, circa 1990 (Box 56)
  - Printed materials, 1979-2001 (Box 56)
  - Printed materials, 1979-2001 (Box 56)
  - Publishing contracts and paperwork, 1989-2002 (Box 56)
  - Research materials: epilepsy, 2002-2003 (Box 56)
  - Resume, 1993 (Box 57)
  - Scrapbook, circa 1951-1953 (Box 57)
  - Screenplay: Miller, Don Ethan, "Dark Lady", 1989 (Box 57)
  - Screenplay: Miller, Don Ethan, "Dark Lady", 1991 (Box 57)
  - Screenplay: Miller, Don Ethan, "Dragon Bones", 1993 (Box 57)
  - Screenplay: Miller, Don Ethan, "Forbidden City", 1992 (Box 57)
  - Script: Klemenchich, Katie, "The Dark Matter", 2000 (Box 57)
  - SDS reunion, 1986 (Box 57)
  - Typescript: Barber, David, untitled, circa 2003 (Box 57)
  - Typescript: Barber, David, untitled, circa 2003 (Box 57)
  - Typescript: Barber, David, untitled, circa 2003 (Box 57)
- Series 7: Audio-Visual, 1966-2000
  - Audio cassette: Assassination of JFK: The Garrison Interview, part 1, undated (Box 59)
    Produced by Andrew Phillips and David Mendelsohn.
  - Audio cassette: Assassination of JFK: The Garrison Interview, part 2, undated (Box 59)
  - Audio cassette: Garrison, undated (Box 59)
  - Audio cassette: Garrison, undated (Box 59)
    Parts 1-2.
  - Audio cassette: Garrison, undated (Box 59)
    Parts 3-4.
  - Audio cassette: Garrison and Mary Howell, 1991 (Box 60)
  - Audio cassette: General Reinhard Gehlen: The CIA Connection, 1990 (Box 60)
    Jeff Young interviewing Mary Ellen Reese, author of Reinhard Gehlen: The Nazi Connection.
  - Audio cassette: JFK Assassination: An Interview with Carl Oglesby, 1992 May 27 (Box 59)
    Produced by Bob Young
  - Audio cassette: Tipton, John, 1984 (Box 60)
    Concerning Klaus Barbie.
  - Audio cassette: "Uncle Sam and the Swastika", 1990 (Box 60)
  - Audio reel to reel: Oglesby, Carl, Lecture at Antioch, 1966 Apr 10 (Box 58)
  - Slides: JFK lectures and talks, various dates (Box 61-62)
    Slides used by Oglesby in his presentations on the JFK assassination.
  - Video tape: Agee, Philip and Stockwell, John, undated (Box 58)
    Both former members of the CIA.
  - Video tape: Alois Brunner: The Last Nazi, undated (Box 59)
  - Video tape: Beyond JFK: The Question of Conspiracy, 1992 (Box 59)
  - Video cassette: "Gehlen", undated (Box 58)
  - Video tape: "Gerry Patrick Hemming Panel", 1996 (Box 58)
    November in Dallas Conference
  - Video tape: JFK Assassination, undated (Box 58)
    Featuring Carl Oglesby.
  - Video tape: Kent State and the Transformation of a nation: A People's History of Kent, undated (Box 58)
  - Video tape: LBJ: A Closer Look, 1998 (Box 58)
  - Video tape: "Making Sense of the Sixties", 1991 (Box 58)
    Excerpts featuring Oglesby in the PBS special.
  - Video tape: "The Men Who Killed JFK", 1991 (Box 58)
  - Video tape: "The Murder of JFK: Confession of an Assassin, 1996 (Box 58)
  - Video tape: Nazi Connection, undated (Box 60)
  - Video tape: "Oglesby on JFK", 2000 Nov 22 (Box 60)
  - Video tape: "Orville Nix Film/JFK", undated (Box 58)
  - Video tape: Political History and the JFK Assassination, 1997 (Box 58)
  - Video tape: Remembering Vietnam, circa 2000 (Box 60)
    Featuring Bernardine Dohrn, Sue Eanet Klonsky, Carl Oglesby, Robert Pardun, Paul Potter; produced and directed by Helen Garvey. An SDS Oral History video, based on interview for Rebels with a Cause, a documentary film about Students for a Democratic Society.